Guy Louden is an Australian artist and curator living in Fremantle/Walyalup and born in Toronto. He has managed and founded experimental galleries and curated major exhibitions. His artwork has been exhibited in Sydney, Melbourne, Perth, regionally and online.

Education

- 2018 Master of Art Curating, University of Sydney 2012-13
- Master of Arts (Art History), University of Manchester 2008-11
- Bachelor of Arts (Fine Arts, English), University of Western Australia • 2009-10 Study abroad scholarship University of California, LA

Exhibitions (selected)

- Co-curator and Artist,

 Preppers, Fremantle Arts Centre,
 2019
- Artist, *Spring1883*, Sydney, 2019
- Artist, Network Archeology,
 Cool Change Contemporary, 2019
- Artist, WROL, Bus Projects, 2018
- Artist and Co-curator, SHTF, Firstdraft, 2017
- Artist, Preppers, Polizia, 2017
- Curator and Artist, Bye, Success, 2016
- Curator, No Confidence, Perth International Arts Festival, 2016
- Curator, *Theatres*, Perth

International Arts Festival, 2015

• Curator, *Specific Gravity*, Moana Project Space, 2015

Publications (selected)

- Essay, *Frictionless*: Dan McCabe, Outer Space ARI, 2019
- Catalogue Text, Memories of the

Network Age, Cool Change, 2019

- Exhibition Exegesis, No Confidence: PIAF Visual Arts Guide, 2016
- Catalogue Essay, *Khazi*: Lilly Kaiser, Moana Project Space, 2015
- Exhibition Exegesis, *Theatres*: PIAF Guide, 2015
- Essay, *Hyperborea*, Free Range, 2014
- Catalogue Essay, Warning: Simon Finn, Moana Project Space, 2013

Residencies + Prizes

- The Churchie National Emerging Art Prize, IMA, Brisbane, 2020
- Fremantle Arts Centre, 2017
- Curatorial Exchange, hosted by Artspace, 2016

Professional Experience

- Assistant Gallery Curator, Heathcote Cultural Precinct, 2019-
- Senior Technician, Carriageworks, 2018-2019
- Art Install Technician, Fremantle Arts Centre, 2017
- Artist Field Officer/GA, Warakurna Artists, 2017
- Art Install Technician, Wesfarmers Collection, 2016, 2019
- Artist Field Officer, Martumili Arts, 2016
- Founder/Program Manager, Success, 2015
- Director, Moana Project Space, 2014-2017